seomanualsubmission.com 2019-05-20

# Legal & Privacy Policy of RS Seo Solution

## **Privacy Policy**

My Company RS Seo Solution​ We, operates ​http://www.seomanualsubmission.com RS Seo Solution. This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of the Site. We use your Personal Information only for providing and improving the Site. By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.

**What information do we collect?**

While using our Site, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to your name ("Personal Information").

We collect information from you when you register on our site or fill out a form.

Wehn ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name or email addresses. you may, however, visit our site anonymously.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * Fulfill your order
  * Send you an order confirmation
  * Assess the needs of your business to determine suitable products
  * Send product updates or warranty information
  * Respond to customer service requests
  * Administer your account
  * Send you a newsletter
  * Respond to your questions and concerns
  * Display content based upon your interests
  * To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * To improve customer service (Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service request and support needs)
  * To process transactions - Your information, wether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or services requested by the customer.
  * To send periodic emails - The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.
  * Note : If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you access your personal information.

**Cookies**

  Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer's hard drive. 

Like many sites, we use "cookies" to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Site.

**Log Data**

Like many site operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Site.

This Log Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics. 

In addition, we may use third party services such as Google Analytics that collect, monitor and analyze this.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

we do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights property, or safety. However, non-personallyidentifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**

Occassionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liablitiy for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Security**

The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**What are the top benefits of RS Seo Solution reseller program?**

  * Fully automated reseller solution.
  * 100% White labeled reseller program that allows you to sell our services in your own brand name. Our white labeled reseller solution will allow your customers to place their orders directly to your company through the reseller website we create for you and receive all the reports in your company name.
  * You are in total control. You will be interacting with your customers directly under your own brand name.
  * You decide your profits. You have total freedom to decide on the pricing at which you would like to offer our services to your customers and we will never interfere.
  * You will get up to 30% discount on all the services except for complete link building solutions, On Page Optimization Service and all SMO Services for which you will get 10% discount.
  * You can pay as you go and there is no huge initial investment required.
  * You can choose to sell the services in any currency using our multi-currency option.
  * Customer privacy 100% guaranteed.

**What are the backend features included in the reseller website?**

When you enter our reseller program, we will create a highly robust backend through which you will be able to run the entire business in an efficient and hassle free way. Our reseller backend includes the following features:

  * Email customization feature to customize email correspondence with every order.
  * Ability to choose the services that you would like to sell.
  * View complete list of orders
  * Customer management
  * Order management
  * Price management with the ability to set your own prices
  * Multi currency selection
  * Integrated payment solution
  * Offers management such as creation of coupon codes
  * Service report customization including look and feel of the reports generated.
  * Ability to select alerts for customer communication
  * Service plan customization with the ability to choose your own plan names and add description of each plan
  * Order search feature
  * Option to view customer invoices
  * Option to view order details
  * Credit status check feature
  * Three Default Payment Gateway options to receive payments on your reseller website - PayPal, 2Checkout, MoneyBookers. On demand payment gateway integration of your choice.

**How much does our reseller program cost?**

You can start your SEO business with as little as $1499 which includes designing of your reseller website, conversion of PSD design to HTML, HTML to PHP, integration of shopping cart, frontend and backend control panel integration and the content for the entire website.

**What is included in the above initial cost?**

We will design a unique reseller website which includes creation of 12 types of pages such as Homepage, Inner page, Registration page, Login page, Customer control panel, etc.

Integration of shopping cart. Here our experienced PHP team will integrate the shopping cart and the services offered through reseller website. The shopping cart will be integrated as per our white label reseller model whereby you will receive directly all the payments sent by your customers and RS Seo Solution will receive the order information.  
Comprehensive testing of all the forms and notification functionalities present in the reseller website prior to the handing over of the reseller website to you.  
Reseller website content written by highly experienced and professional writers (approx. 7000 words).

**Are there any other hidden costs?**

No. You just need to pay this one time fee of $1499. For the execution of the orders from your customers, your account must have the required credit.

**What is the time required to set up our reseller service?**

The entire process will take anywhere between 15 to 25 days depending on how fast you respond during the website design process on design approvals.

**What does the reseller website include?**

  * Frontend - This is where the services will be showcased and customers will be placing their orders in the frontend.
  * Customer control panel - Customers will interact with you during the order execution stage through this panel including invoice management through this panel.
  * Reseller backend - This is where you will control the reseller options. You can choose the services that you would like to sell, pricing of the services, customer tracking, etc. To know more about complete functionality please check reseller website backend features

**How does RS Seo Solution reseller program work?**

RS Seo Solution has created a highly hassle free reseller solution that. After the completion of the reseller website including shopping cart integration, front end and backend setup you need to go through the following initial setup.  
Initial Setup:  
You need to setup the basic configurations (under reseller settings) like website URL, Email Id from which customers should receive all the email communications, etc. You need to login to your reseller control panel and set your own pricing for all the services and service plans.  
Choose your preferred mode or method of payment from your customers. Customize the look and feel of the reports your customers will be receiving. With these easy few steps you are ready to sell our services and your reseller website is all set for the game. When your customers place the orders through the reseller website, you will get all the payments sent by your customers and the orders will come to us. If you have enough credit in your account your customer orders will be automatically processed.

**What will happen if my reseller account does not have enough or any credit?**

There is nothing to worry. You will still be able to receive the payment from your customers and your customers will be able to fill the requirements form as usual. Insufficient or lack of credit in the reseller account will not affect the order functionalities. However, all the orders will be locked in your reseller account. You will be receiving email notification from us on the credit status. Once the reseller deposits the money in his or her reseller account all the orders will be processed.

**As a reseller, am I allowed to fix my own pricing for RS Seo Solution services?**

Yes, you are absolutely free for fixing your own pricing for the services. You have 100% control on the prices at which you would like to sell RS Seo Solution services.

**Who provides customer support?**

Reseller handles all sales related support. All the service related queries posted in the message board by customers will be replied by RS Seo Solution staff.

**Will the customer ever come to know that RS Seo Solution is the original service provider?**

No, your customers will never come to know that the orders are executed by RS Seo Solution. We have very strict reseller privacy policy. Added to that, we also sing Non Disclosure Agreement to this effect.

Can an existing website be integrated?

Yes, we can integrate the shopping cart to your existing website.

What are the hosting requirements for reseller website?

  * PHP 5.2.0 (or Higher)
  * Linux Server - Apache Latest version
  * Mod_rewrite function.
  * CURL - ADD/UPDATE/DELETE Support
  * PHP Simple XML

**Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions selection establishing the use, desclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website and http://www.seomanualsubmission.com/termsnconditions.php

**Your consent**

by using our site, your consent to our privacy policy.

**Change to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

This policy was last modified on 18th June 2016.

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

http://www.seomanualsubmission.com  
S-6, Shri Gopal Nagar  
Gopalpura Byepass, Jaipur 302018,  
Rajasthan, India  
info@seomanualsubmission.com
